[{"answer": "What", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "My heart's in that place", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You're tellin' me there's no place you'd rather be other than here", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "If I was in that place right now, I wouldn't be thinking about here. See the difference", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "But I'm here, I know I'm here, I don't like being here, but I can't be anyplace else because I look around and I see all this shit. How do you get around that?! That's what I'm asking", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "But I'm here, I know I'm here, I don't like being here, but I can't be anyplace else because I look around and I see all this shit. How do you get around that?! That's what I'm asking", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Focus", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah. You surprise me sometimes. Here I think you're just a hard case and I discover you've got a heart of gold.  You're an organ donor. That's really nice. The only problem is, they'll never use your best parts", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Hey, don't get me wrong. I was just surprised that we had something in common... Besides what we have in common", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What if I was", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Maybe I got plans", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yes, he did", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Sorry, my friend, can't do it", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You gotta get written permission from the Chief", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Tell me about it. You know how much I got left", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I think you just like fuckin' her", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Nobody ever wants to be punished for what they've done. It's just a new concept. But I still think our defense is reasonable. I don't believe, under the condition you were in, that you were responsible for your actions", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "If you hadn't been carrying the gun, you might be dead", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "We need to talk", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Not just a second, now", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I said", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "...she's supposed to testify. She got scared, thinks somebody might kill her, so she's hidin'. That's why I want you to find her. If somebody is tryin' to pop her, I don't want anyone knowin' where she is. my friend eyes my friend. He doesn't believe anything anybody tells him. Especially in his business", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "How long I got", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Shit, two fuckin' days", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "No, I'm not fuckin' with you. Are you fuckin' with me?", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Know what", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Based on what", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Who provided you with the description", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "4356 17th Street. Number 37", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Close? Sort of", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "No... I don't think so", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I ahh... drove", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Was there a reason you parked so far away", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Was there anyone else on the street besides you", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What did you do then? Did you call the police, 911", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You went home. Straight home", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Don't hold your breath", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I know she'll talk", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Look, a guy comes in, says bail her out, gives me the money, I do it. That's how I make my living, I bail fuckin' people outa jail. You wait with me", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Yeah, right. Cops bail people outa jail all the time. Doesn't there seem to be a dichotomy there for you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Where's my friend", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You're gonna find him?  Right... I don't know a fuckin' thing", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You had to do the right thing", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What do I want", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Forceps.  Just like old times", "docId": "Gang-Related.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Lucky to have a donor. Never would've survived the night. Have a suture ready", "qsentId": 48}]